take a walk D I don't want to have to
kick your ass okay Adam this is so dumb
all right I'd like to get to this photo
shoot on time try being a pacifist I'll
be a pacifist I'll pass my fist through
your face that's not possible oh isn't
it huh is that possible you doing I'm
serious is this
possible dropped 30 spots in the
rankings because of you yeah CLA graph's
gone feel like a threw away my whole
early 20s for nothing sucks for you but
it's not about you it's about me in this
chunk no Adam you're not fighting tur
you're fighting
me good luck B Adam who got Adam nobody
got Adam Adam over here all right what
about you wait H is not even fighting I
want that's it best off best off you
want me you got me
dude oh I'm BL o hya hya get over
yourself
dude good luck oh thanks man oh God my
[Music]
eyes take it from me even a blind man
can land a punch if he sees it in his
mouth I
[Music]
first my go are you okay it's just my
face it's okay I'm so sorry this is your
fault